<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recommoning – </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Recommoning</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    
	  <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/250722-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 23:23:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/250722-intro/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Well, I’ve been accepted on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cardiff.ac.uk/study/postgraduate/taught/courses/course/environment-and-development-msc&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;MSc in Environment and Development&lt;/a&gt; at Cardiff University, I have a potential mixed enterprise agroforestry site in mind, and I‘ve had some good feedback on a grant application. 🎉&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The name of the site is &lt;mark&gt;Recommoning&lt;/mark&gt;, because I think there needs to be a fundamental rethinking of how society is organised to tackle the nature and nature climate crisis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;For a very long time, the intellectual consensus has been that we can no longer ask Great Questions. Increasingly, it’s looking like we have no other choice&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;cite&gt;David Graeber, &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Debt:_The_First_5,000_Years&#34;&gt;Debt: the first 5,000 years&lt;/a&gt; pp19&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I use &lt;a href=&#34;https://obsidian.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Obsidian&lt;/a&gt; a lot for my day-to-day note taking and writing, so I’m using it to publish thoughts and organisation to this website, using the most excellent &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; static site generator and the rather nice documentation and blog theme &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/imfing/hextra&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Hextra&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A big thank you to Doug for the stimulating conversations, which prompted this website because I wanted to put my reading list online! And a massive thank you to Antonia Malchik for all the inspiration from &lt;a href=&#34;https://antonia.substack.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;On the Commons&lt;/a&gt;, helping to rekindle why I’m doing what I’m doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested, the source code is available here &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/growdigital/jaker.uk&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;github.com/growdigital/jaker.uk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
